a herd of sheep grazing in a field
Nelore Cattle - Bos taurus indicus
a wolf standing in the middle of a forest
Gray Wolf - Canis lupus
a cat sitting in the snow on a snowy day
Domestic Cat - Felis catus
a red deer stag in a rut with hinds
Red Deer - Cervus elaphus
a red fox standing next to a tree
Red Fox - Vulpes vulpes
a ram standing on a hillside
Alpine Ibex - Capra ibex
a white polar wolf sitting on top of a rock
Arctic Wolf - Canis lupus arctos
a red panda is sitting on a log near a tree
Red Panda - Ailurus fulgens
a brown and white striped tiger standing next to a tree
Siberian Tiger - Panthera tigris altaica
an elephant walking through a grassy field
African Elephant - Loxodonta africana
a brown and white squirrel eating some grass
Red Squirrel - Sciurus vulgaris
a deer walking through a forest with a bunch of trees
Deer - Cervidae
a brown and black lizard sitting on a rock
Bearded Dragon - Pogona vitticeps
a frame of a bee hive
Honeybee - Apis mellifera
a giraffe walking in the savannah
Giraffe - Giraffa camelopardalis
a herd of sheep grazing on a lush green hillside
Nelore Cattle - Bos taurus indicus
a brown and white striped tiger laying on a dirt ground
Bengal Tiger - Panthera tigris tigris
a small black bear is standing in the trees
Silvery Gibbon - Hylobates moloch
a large black and white photo of a gorilla
Western Lowland Gorilla - Gorilla gorilla gorilla
a large owl sitting on top of a tree branch
Long-Eared Owl - Asio otus
a close up picture of a cute little brown and white cat
Eurasian Lynx - Lynx lynx
two young leopards are standing next to each other
Snow Leopard - Panthera uncia
a small brown cheetah sitting on top of a grass covered field
Juvenile Cheetah - Acinonyx jubatus